[eerie music playing]
[parking brake clicks]
[door unlocks]
[woman] Mr. Governor!
- [Miura] Good to see you. - Thank you. Go ahead, sir.
- [woman 2] Welcome back. - [man 1] The governor's here?
- [man 2] Mr. Governor! - [cheering]
[man 2] Congratulations!
You work so hard. Thank you all very much.
[volunteers] Thank you.
As you know, the most important speech is the one I'll give tomorrow.
Let's make it count!
The election is upon us. Two more days.
It's the final push. [laughs]
Let's keep it up and put on a show!
- [cheering] - [volunteers] Yeah!
[man 3 gasps]
[low, sinister music playing]
[volunteers screaming and panicking]
[music building]
[tense, dramatic music playing]
Kaho, hey!
Hey! You okay? Are you hurt?
But just look over there. Look.
[man grunting]
- [distant scream] - [Miura] Go check inside!
I'm fine! Go check inside!
[man] Right away!
- [Miura groaning] - [man] You okay?
- [Miura groaning] - [siren wailing]
We should get out of here. Come on, let's go.
[newscaster] Breaking news.
The Metropolitan Police Department is reporting
that the Human Vapor has attacked Governor Miura's campaign office in Tokyo.
Three have been reported dead in the attack,
with multiple others injured, some in critical condition.
Governor Miura was in the headquarters at the time and was injured in the attack
Miura ordered the Human Vapor to attack us.
He's the reason my brother's dead.
I just don't
Why would he do that?
I don't get it.
[newscaster] five more dead
[Kenji] He was ordering the Human Vapor's attacks.
So then, who put the hit out on him?
Wait. Fujita's camera is still
We were trying to find out the Human Vapor's identity.
He set up a camera!
It would still be there, and it should still be working.
It might've caught the person who ordered the attack on Miura.
- [tires screech] - [horn beeping]
- Is he okay? - What's going on?
I don't like this.
- [crashing] - [man yelling in pain]
[man choking]
[haunting music droning]
[music fades out]
[Kyoko] What now?
Gimme a second.
[ominous music playing]
Huh?
- Hey. - What do you want, huh?
- [man 1] You fuckin' deaf? - [man 2] Get outta here!
- [man 2 grunts] - Where you goin'?
Hey. I asked you a question, brother!
- [blows landing2] - [wooden plank clatters]
[heavy thud]
[Kyoko] Through here.
The coast is clear.
He'll be back soon. We have to hurry.
Where'd Fujita put the camera?
This way, I think.
[Miura] In about two hours' time, I need you for something.
There will be a number of volunteers at Takeshi Miura's campaign headquarters.
That's your target.
Kill three people there.
After that,
I need you to kill all the homeless people in front of the station.
Leave none of them alive.
And one more thing.
[laughs]
Don't kill me.
[Kaho] This guy is just the worst.
[Kirishima] This station insists on reporting about Human Vapor,
all day, every day.
You are terrifying all the voters,
So now more and more of them are calling for Miura to be reelected.
An attack in downtown Tokyo,
And yet Miura's approval rating is just gonna keep going up.
What?
In the wake of an attack or a tragedy, we all hope for stability.
The governor only stands to benefit from this.
Wait, what are you saying?
[Kyoko sighs] People are afraid.
An unstoppable force kills again,
And no one knows what to do.
But if Miura stands strong and leads,
He'll be seen as a hero. He'll win by a landslide.
So you're saying in order to win the election,
He condemned his own staff to die?
Is that really surprising though?
We know he doesn't value life, don't we?
[Kenji sighs]
[Kyoko] People are worthless to him.
We're nothing but human fuel.
[Kaito] Hey. Hey!
There's someone inside.
[footsteps approaching]
[Kaho] Hmm?
Let's go.
[Kyoko] Wait, wait!
I have an idea.
You.
What do you think you're doing?
What was that? Get him!
Kaito, get me some chain.
[grunting and shouting]
[Riki] Get him! He's just one guy!
- Hurry, Kaho. - Okay.
[grunting and shouting]
[frantic string music playing]
- [Kaito yells] - [heavy thud]
[Kenji groans]
[music fades]
[Riki] What the hell did you do?
Is he dead? Oh shit.
[mysterious music playing]
[Kenji groans weakly]
[music fades out]
[groaning]
The world will soon know my true power.
- The world will soon know my true power. - [foreboding industrial music playing]
[phone ringing]
[phone continues ringing]
Hello?
Hey. Um, we've run into a complication.
[Miura] What happened? Where are you?
The abandoned warehouse.
We think they taped the whole thing.
What? What thing?
You gave an order to the Vapor guy.
You did, right?
And while you were doing that, you were secretly being recorded.
- [drip stand rattles] - [groans]
Where's the footage?
[grunts]
[Riki] Don't know.
A detective called Okamoto was here with the video camera.
We caught him. He's with us.
I need to know where that recording went.
Ask him, but keep him alive.
Will do. We'll get the info. Leave it to us.
And don't do anything
- [call disconnects] - [tuts]
[sighs]
[music fades]
[exhales eagerly]
[man] You don't have to worry about that at least.
You've pulled ahead of Kirishima. Up 7%.
We've got this in the bag, sir.
Be that as it may, it's not over.
We'll cement our lead tomorrow any way we can.
[sighs]
[groans, grunts]
[harsh, distorted music playing]
[Kenji grunting]
[Riki laughing]
[Riki] You wanna talk yet?
Just tell us where the recording ended up.
- [Kenji struggling] - [Riki] Where did you put it?
[Riki grunts]
[Riki sighs] You really need to start talking.
I promised I'd keep you alive,
But I've never been keen on promises.
- Where's the fun in that? - [Kenji grunting]
[Riki laughing]
- [Riki grunts] - [Kenji groans]
[Kenji breathing raggedly]
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
[Kaito] Just fuckin' tell us!
- [kicking] - You listening?
- Where is the recording? - [Miura] Hey!
Let's all just take a breath. You've gone too far.
Look what you did.
You're just like your father. The spitting image.
Huh? Down to your fat little baby cheeks.
- So what did you find out? - [sighs] Nothing.
- Gimme that. - Huh?
[pistol clicks]
- [man yelps] - [Riki] What the hell?
[crashing]
[Riki] Sada.
- Sada? - [Miura sighs]
Okamoto? Am I saying that right?
Great to meet you.
I'm Miura, governor of Tokyo.
[Kenji gags] I thought
You were with Mufu.
Such a pathetic organization.
[sighs] Very well.
I wanna tell you a story I heard once in Romania.
[Kenji breathing heavily]
Miguel was a lovely, carefree young man
Whose life's work was running a bee farm.
The hell are you talking about?
[Miura] Every bee
Has its own role in the colony.
The bees who defend the hive
And those who make honey.
But every single one
Works, lives, and gives its life to the queen bee.
The queen has a big task.
She mates,
Expands their numbers, and grows the hive.
And humans
Have exactly the same roles.
From the moment you're born,
Your life becomes one of work for a great machine.
You live and die as its fuel.
Do you understand now?
We need the fuel.
We need the human fuel.
[Kenji exhales]
Of course, a great machine needs great people to run it.
Don't you agree?
And you actually think you're one of those great people?
- That's such a fucking joke! - [Miura laughs]
Your machine is nothing, and you're living in a fantasy world.
[Kenji breathing heavily]
- [Kenji groans] - Look.
Since you asked so nicely,
I'll tell you what part you have to play.
You're going to stand beside me.
I need a new right hand,
Now that Sakamoto's dead.
Together, we'll conquer the world.
- [Kenji spits] - Ugh!
- [Miura groans] - [Kenji coughs]
[Miura chuckles]
Such spirit.
That's too bad.
Tell me who has the footage.
You didn't come here alone, did you?
[sighs] Start talking.
You have five seconds.
Five. Time to breathe.
Four. Breathe in.
Three. Breathe out.
Two. Time's up.
Okay! Wait! I'll tell you! I'll tell you what you wanna know.
[Kenji coughing]
I'll just I need a second to breathe.
- [Miura] Where is it? - [Kenji groans]
- Where the hell is it? - [Kenji groans]
[Kenji wheezes and gags]
You're too late.
Kyoko Kono. She has it now.
She's long gone.
She's going to air it.
All the networks will.
You won't win.
- You're done, Kai. - [Miura tutting]
That's what you think.
[funereal orchestral music playing]
I've got an ace in the hole.
[Kenji yells] Kai!
No matter what happens, I'll stop you.
I'll make you pay for everything you've done!
I'll make you pay!
[Miura grunting]
Shut up! Don't you ever stop talking? Just shut up!
[Kenji gags]
["Ellie My Love" by Southern All Stars playing]
[Human Vapor] Listener,
Please,
Make a wish.
I want you
To find Kyoko Kono and the footage she took from here.
Make sure the data's destroyed,
Then I want you to kill Ms. Kono.
[Kenji grunts]
[Miura] Mr. Okamoto knows too much. Do whatever you want with him.
[muffled shouting]
- [Riki] Get him up. - [Kaito] You got it.
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
[song fades]
[Miura] That's your target. Kill three people there.
- After that - [Kaho] This guy's just the worst.
[mysterious music playing]
[Kaito] Hey. Hey!
There's someone inside.
[footsteps approaching]
[Kaho] Hmm?
Let's go.
Wait, wait!
I have an idea.
Kaho and I will get outta here,
Get the video out to the public as soon as we can.
What I need from you, Kenji
Can you figure out some way to make Miura send Ren after me?
You can't be serious. If I do that, you'll--
Trust me.
I can do this.
I know exactly how to stop him.
How, Kyoko?
We have to end this before he kills again.
Okay?
Please, trust me.
[breathing heavily]
Parfinee time.
[dark, dramatic music playing]
HUMAN VAPOR
[mysterious music playing]
TOKYO GOVERNOR CANDIDATE KAZUMI KIRISHIMA
[Kyoko] There she is.
Hey, Kaho.
It's gonna be all right.
Okay.
Right, I'm going in.
[soft music playing]
[Kirishima] It's the day before the election.
We've had our ups and downs,
But let's do our best and fight until the very end.
- I'm counting on you! - [volunteers] Yes, ma'am!
[Kaho, softly] Excuse me
Sorry, hello?
Pardon the interruption, Ms. Kirishima.
I, um
My name's Kaho Fujikawa.
I'm a video streamer and I, uh, would like to
If it's possible to speak to Ms. Kirishima just for a few minutes?
I have some questions for her. Is that okay?
[man] This isn't a good time. We're about to go to a rally.
[Kaho] Wait, wait! Hang on!
It's about Miura!
- [man] Miss, I'm sorry, but - It's important.
- [suspenseful music playing] - [detective 1] Bag it.
[Yoshida] We're seizing anything related to the case of the Human Vapor.
- [detective 2] Got it. - [camera clicks]
[detective 1] Okay, now the laptop.
[phone vibrating]
KONO
[tense music playing]
I'm alone. Where have you been?
Tatsuya, you told me you wanted to be a journalist no matter what.
- I did. - Then listen.
I'm gonna send you something important. Get it on the air, now.
[Tatsuya] What? You want me to what?
[Riki breathes shakily]
[Riki breathes deeply]
[metal scraping]
[chilling music playing]
It is time
For the Parfinee. Prepare yourselves.
[together] Yes, boss.
[Kenji panting]
[Riki] Now, where to begin?
Wow. You have such pretty eyes.
[Kenji breathing heavily]
We'll leave those pretty eyes for the very end.
How's that sound?
I'll start with the ears instead.
[Riki laughing]
- [Kenji grunting] - [Riki] How many cuts will it take?
Should we start from the top?
On second thought, let's do the bottom.
[Kenji grunts]
[jarring dramatic music playing]
- [men shouting] - [Kenji grunting]
- [crunching] - [man 1 groans]
[grunting]
[man 2 grunting]
[man 3 yells]
[Kenji yells] Who's next?
[Kenji grunting angrily]
[man 4 grunts]
[man 4 choking]
[Kenji breathing heavily]
[Kaito yells]
[Riki panting, grunting]
[Riki yells]
[gunshots]
[Kaito choking]
[Riki yelling]
[Riki grunting]
[Riki groaning weakly]
Tell me what a Parfinee is, you asshole.
[music fades]
[Kenji groans]
[groans]
[exhales heavily]
[Kenji panting]
[keys jangling]
[Kenji breathing heavily]
[Miura] a number of volunteers at Takeshi Miura's campaign headquarters.
That's your target.
- Kill three people there. - [Kirishima] What?
Is this recording real?
Yeah, I assure you.
This should be enough to stop him for good.
You have to go public with it.
There's not enough time to prove it's real.
It's political suicide if it turns out to be fake.
You'll be run out not just of the election but politics forever.
- Miss, I have to insist you leave. Now. - [news report playing in background]
[woman] Come along, miss.
- [Kaho] Hang on! - [man] Just leave, please.
No, stop! Are you trying to win the election or aren't you?
- [newscaster] Kirishima is trailing - [Kaho] You're polling behind him, right?
[Kirishima] She's right. We can't win unless something changes.
Let's bet it all on this video.
We can release it on our channel right away.
No, no. Ms. Kirishima, please reconsider. It's not a good idea.
After what you just saw,
You're telling me you want us to stay silent
When he's killing his own constituents?
[man] I think someone else should release the video first.
- [Kirishima] We can't afford to wait! - [dreamy music playing]
We'll leak it to the media! [echoing]
[Kirishima] No one would touch this the day before an election!
[inaudible]
I can stream the video, on my channel.
[music fades out]
And once it's out, all you'd have to do is repost it.
[determined music playing]
- I've got more copies. - Great.
- This is wild. - You got that right.
Gruesome stuff.
"Radiation."
- [director] What are you doing? - Oh, Director.
All this material was sent to us by Kyoko.
What?
- When was this? - Just now, by email.
- [woman] The Human Vapor. There he is. - [man 1] What?
[woman] Ren Tsutsumida.
- [man 1] Ren Tsutsumida. - [man 2] Ren Tsutsumida.
[phone ringing out]
- [breathing heavily] - [phone ringing out]
[Kyoko] Hello?
Miura, he
He sent the Human Vapor out to kill you.
[panting] Is he there?
Thankfully, not yet.
The video will be online real soon.
Kyoko, where are you?
[Kyoko] I'm heading to the old JNT building.
I'll lure Ren there and stop him.
Yeah, all right. I'll meet you there.
Kenji.
You're gonna bring Miura to justice, won't you?
[Kenji] What?
Get revenge for all of us.
It's all up to you now.
Kyoko.
Please, Kenji.
- [taps phone] - [phone clatters softly]
[breathing heavily]
[woman] First of all, I need to thank you for coming out to our final rally.
TAKESHI MIURA LOVE, LOVE
[woman] Thank you so much!
And now, the moment you've all been waiting so patiently for.
- On this final day - Takeshi!
[woman] we'd love for you to hear one last time
From the current Governor of Tokyo.
- Let's hear it for Takeshi Miura! - [crowd cheering]
[Miura] My friends, I've been through hell.
And I'm back, stronger than ever!
[crowd cheering]
Let us keep our dreams alive!
[music fades out]
This one's for you, Fujita.
[woman] And three, two, one.
[intriguing music playing]
Welcome to horror paradise!
So what's up, killers? Are you ready?
I know what you're thinking.
"Who's that girl? I know that voice."
Oh! It's me!
I'm Kaho, Fujita's sister! So good to meet all of you!
It's my first time on this side of the camera.
I'm sure you can tell.
LIVE
So, not only will today's live stream be a memorial for our boy
and my sweet, dear, nerdy brother Fujita,
but we'll also be airing explosive footage of the Human Vapor.
Smash that like button and share!
Ready, killers? Here we go.
This is super-exclusive footage,
Brought to you by none other than our own god of fear and pain.
He gave his life for you!
[crowd cheering]
[Miura] We've accomplished much in such a short time.
Over the past four years, crime has dropped by 10%,
And homelessness in the city has been cut very nearly in half!
[crowd cheering]
Thank you so much!
We couldn't have done it without you!
And that's not all!
To help stabilize the falling birthrate,
No more waiting lists for daycare!
[crowd cheering]
For households with two or more children, my government
[crowd falls silent]
Will provide, per month,
50,000 yen for child allowance!
- Wait, what? - [crowd cheering]
And today I am proud to announce
That we will make university tuition free as well!
So,
These three measures will be the basis of our governance.
The people of Tokyo will have what they crave
BREAKING NEWS: GOVERNOR MIURA ACCUSED IN VIDEO
- I We won't stop! - [tense music playing]
THERE SHOULD BE VOLUNTEER STAFF
[crowd murmuring]
WREAK HAVOC KILL THREE PEOPLE
Until all of us
[crowd shouting angrily]
[crowd jeering]
[woman 1] Is this true? Get the hell out of here! We trusted you!
He's not worth it.
[Miura] Please, everybody! Please!
[woman 2] We believed in you! Get the hell out!
- [crowd shouting] - You lied to all of us!
KAHO FUJIKAWA: "MY BROTHER SACRIFICED HIMSELF"
- [crowd shouting] - [woman 3] What's going on?
You! Come here! You wanna tell me what the hell is going on?!
Let's just take it easy.
We'll head back and figure something out. Sound good?
[Miura yells]
[yells, then sighs]
- [banging outside] - [Miura gasps]
[banging continues]
[tense music building]
[woman] It's got a shocking number of views already.
Your style's a little unorthodox, but it certainly works well.
- [music fades] - Okay. Well, thanks.
Yeah, I I appreciate it.
- [man] How's it looking? - [woman] Fine.
- [man] Ready? - [woman] I'm good to go.
[man] All right, then. In three
[Kirishima] Hello, everyone. I'm sure most of you know me, Kazumi Kirishima.
- This is an emergency live stream. - [gentle music playing]
I imagine by now, many of you will have seen today's stream
From Fujita and Kaho's Horror Zone.
It's hard to believe. I know I have trouble believing it
[speech fades]
[poignant music playing]
[sighs softly]
[tense, dramatic music playing]
[tires screech]
[Kenji grunts]
[Kenji panting]
[guard] Excuse me, sir? Sir, hey!
[Kenji breathing heavily]
- [guard] Stop! - [Kenji panting]
[men grunt]
[tense, dramatic music continues]
[Michiko] Hey, you're back! You all right?
What happened? You're hurt.
Hey! What's going on?
- Kenji, stop! - [Kenji grunts]
Hey! Listen up!
We're arresting Governor Miura.
What? Listen to yourself, Kenji.
You must be out of your mind.
Coming in here covered in blood, screaming about arresting the governor?
Where the hell have you even been?
You know what? It doesn't matter.
Because it's your ex-girlfriend who we're after.
Just bring her here. I'll arrest her myself.
- [Michiko] Wait, stop! Hey! - [Yoshida grunting]
[music builds, then fades]
The footage seems to show Governor Miura allegedly giving the orders
to have some of his campaign staff killed.
MAN ALLEGED TO BE GOVERNOR MIURA
In about two hours' time,
I need you for something.
There will be a number of volunteers at Takeshi Miura's campaign headquarters.
That's your target.
Kill three people there.
After that, I need you to kill all the homeless people in front of the station.
[newscaster] This video was released today via live stream by Kaho Fujikawa,
sister of the now-deceased streamer Fujita Fujikawa.
She claims the murders committed by the Human Vapor
at Miura's campaign headquarters were ordered by the governor himself.
- Get a warrant for Miura, now. - Yes, sir!
[chief] Just wait a second!
[suspenseful music playing]
You know that won't work.
You think this is enough for an arrest warrant?
If we don't do anything, there's a good chance Miura's gonna run.
- You feel good about that, Chief? - If you go after Miura
You better be ready to face the consequences.
Oh, so what? We should just let him get away?
[suspenseful music building]
I'm going.
I'm going with him.
All right, let's move!
[chief sighs]
[scoffs]
- I didn't know that, wow. - It's funny. There are 23 different kinds.
- Twenty-three? - Something like that.
[siren wailing]
- Police! Where's the governor? - [man] You can't storm in!
Warrant's in the mail.
[woman] You're not getting away with this!
- Warrant's coming, okay? - You can't do this!
[Kenji] Miura!
- [music fades] - Where is he?
[man] Right over there.
Or at least he was a minute ago.
[Kenji scoffs]
Set up a perimeter. We gotta find him.
- He's not getting away. - Yes, sir!
- I'll take the stairs. - Yeah.
[music fades out]
[Miura] After all this time, that's it? It's over?
I see. So that's just the way it has to be.
And there's no other way?
I have been loyal for so long. I
Yes, sir.
I understand.
[sighs]
[yells]
[grunts]
[yelling]
[shouts]
That makes me human fuel too, doesn't it?
I see.
[tense, dramatic music playing]
- You go that way! - I'll go with him.
- You can check down there. - Got it.
[shoe squeaks]
[Kenji panting]
[Michiko and Yoshida grunting]
- Get off me! - [Motoyama] Miura's on the roof!
[gunshot over earpiece]
Motoyama?
Motoyama, come in!
- Go! I've got him! - Let go of me! You can't do this to me!
[Yoshida yells]
All right! Fine, fine! Just hang on.
I'm not resisting, okay?
I'm not resisting. You got me! It's fine, just
[bystanders scream]
[Yoshida panting]
[grunting]
[Michiko grunts]
Yoshida. We don't have to fight.
[Yoshida] Huh?
Careful, you're getting cocky, Michiko.
[both grunting]
[Yoshida groans]
[elevator bell dings]
Hurry! Run!
[Michiko grunts, gasps]
[Yoshida grunts]
[panting]
[Michiko wheezing]
[grunts]
[Yoshida grunting]
[both grunting]
[elevator bell dings]
[grunts]
No! No, wait! Wait, wait!
[Yoshida panicking]
[Yoshida screaming]
[Yoshida choking, gasping]
[bones crack]
[tense, dramatic music playing]
[Kenji panting]
Motoyama! Hey! You okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine. He's up there. Go! Hurry!
Motoyama's down, we need medics on the rooftop!
[panting]
Miura!
Oh, Okamoto!
[laughs]
What brings you up here?
[Kenji] End of the line. Give it up.
It's over. You're done.
[Miura] Okamoto.
I met a man once, named Miguel.
He was a musician, played in a band.
He was pretty good too.
Ah
This is gonna take way too long.
See ya.
- [Miura grunting] - [Kenji straining]
[Miura groaning]
Let go of me, dammit! Stop it! Stop it! [grunts]
[straining] I'm not letting you get away again.
[Miura yells, gasps]
Let go of me! Hey! Let go, dammit!
[Miura grunting]
[frenetic orchestral music playing]
[Miura] Unless
You wanna come along?
Well?
[Miura laughing]
[Kenji straining]
[grunts, gasps]
[chief] Okamoto! We've got you!
- [chief grunting] - [Miura] No! Shit! Stop, no!
Let go of me!
[all grunting]
[Miura] Dammit, I want to die! Let go of me!
What are you doing? Get off of me!
Let go! Stop! You can't do this! Ah!
[music softens]
[music fades out]
[panting]
DANGER NO ENTRY
[grunts]
[grunting]
[alarm ringing]
[panting]
[yelps]
[metal crashing]
MAIN POWER ROOM
[panting]
[grunting]
[Kyoko breathing anxiously]
[wistful music playing]
[metal objects clattering]
[whooshing]
[metal clanging]
[wistful music continues]
[automated voice] You have one new message.
[Kyoko] I'm so sorry, Kenji.
I lied to you earlier.
We can't stop Ren. It's impossible.
But I'm going to lock him in a vault.
The one in the basement of the old JNT building.
Whatever happens,
don't let him out.
[whooshing through air ducts]
[Human Vapor howling]
The Human Vapor! This ends now!
[music ends]
[breathing heavily]
[melancholy piano music playing]
[young Kyoko] Ren.
Can I make a wish please, Ren? Can I?
Oh, of course you can.
Go right ahead and make a wish.
Okay, I'm ready to say it.
My wish
Is for you to be my dad, Ren.
[inaudible]
[soft music playing]
[Human Vapor groaning]
- [door rattling] - [Kenji grunting]
Kyoko!
[soft music continues]
[Human Vapor howling]
Thank you!
[ghostly howling]
- [explosion] - [howling fades]
[music fades out]
[gentle piano music playing]
[exhales heavily]
[shocked groan]
[groans]
[gasps]
[yells]
[wails]
[sobs softly]
[newscaster] Many mysteries unsolved in the case of the Human Vapor.
ONE YEAR LATER
New information has emerged regarding a connection between him
and former reporter Kyoko Kono.
Witnesses have revealed that the two individuals in question
were forced into illegal labor at White Center,
and they both lived there during the same period.
This suggests they knew each other before the Human Vapor attacks began.
To this day, their whereabouts remain unknown.
According to sources, one year ago,
an officer and from the Metropolitan Police Department witnessed the moment
Kono the Human Vapor seemingly vanished.
This strange occurrence took place inside a vault
in the basement of the old JNT building.
Police believe the two may have disappeared intentionally
in order to avoid arrest.
[wistful piano music playing]
This is, uh Who are you?
Tatsuya Nishiyama. I'm from JNT.
[Michiko] Right. Yes.
So, how can I help you?
It's a request from the PR office, looking to do a piece on what we do here.
It's for Police 24 Hours or something.
You're doing a stakeout, right?
Go along with her. Feel free to ask whatever you want.
[Michiko] Uh, hold on, Chief?
Good to see you again.
What?
Have we met before?
[Tatsuya] Yeah, a long time ago.
We were working on the Human Vapor.
Huh? Wait.
In the parking lot? In Shizuoka?
That's the one. You got it.
[both chuckle]
- Okay. Shall we head out? - Sure.
[Tatsuya] Wow.
[Michiko] Seriously.
Last year was a lot, wasn't it?
It sure was, yeah.
Could've done with less.
[Kaho] Welcome to horror paradise! Let's go.
How are all you killers doing tonight? Bloody awesome?
[sighs] I can't even believe what I'm seeing.
We are now at ten
million subscribers!
Yay!
Hey, Fujita, did you hear the news?
We did it.
We got here in one year.
It's wild, hmm? But you know what?
We're not finished yet!
Killers, you need to know something about my brother, okay?
Fujita wanted to become the world's number one streamer.
That was his dream.
I'm sorry to say he's threatened to haunt us if you don't subscribe.
So make sure you follow to join Fujita and Kaho's Terror Zone,
and don't forget to ring that bell while you're at it!
Because if you don't support us,
Then the spirit of the man himself will haunt you!
[gasps twice]
Illuminati! How did you find us? [gasps]
I'm so sorry, killers, but that's it for today.
[screams]
"I'm here, my sister!"
[choking]
No! Stop! Get out of my head! No, no! Stop!
"Kaho, I still have so much to say! Don't go!"
Get out of my head! Stop! No!
[music fades out]
KYOKO KONO
["Ellie My Love" by Southern All Stars playing]
[lyrics in Japanese]
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
[lyrics in Japanese]
[exhales deeply]
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
[lyrics in Japanese]
♪ On my mind ♪
♪ In your sight ♪
[lyrics in Japanese]
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
["Ellie My Love" continues]
[lyrics in Japanese]
BASED ON THE MOTION PICTURE "THE HUMAN VAPOR" (1960)
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
[lyrics in Japanese]
♪ On my mind ♪
♪ In your sight ♪
[lyrics in Japanese]
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
[lyrics in Japanese]
♪ On my mind ♪
♪ In your sight ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪ - [lyrics in Japanese]
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ So sweet ♪
♪ Ellie ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, baby ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh, oh, whoa-oh ♪
♪ Oh ♪
[song ends]
[soft, poignant music playing]